Inventory of the Gerald Fried papers, 1941-2014
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Series III. Project Files
  - Sub-series 6. TV Series & TV Movies
    - Roots I
      - Reel-to-reel: "Racines" (in French), 1977 (Box 99)
      - Reel-to-Reel: "Roots" I, 1977 (Box 99)
      - Reel-to-Reel: "Tilo Ming Beteta", 1977 (Box 99)
      - Reel-to-Reel: Wolper "Roots", 1977 (Box 99)
      - Score, Part A, 1976 (Box 79)
      - Score, Part B, 1976 (Box 80)
      - Score, Part C, undated (Box 80)
      - Score, Part D, undated (Box 80)
      - Score, Part E, undated (Box 81)
      - Score, Part F, 1976-1977 (Box 81)
      - Score, Part G, 1976-1977 (Box 82)
      - Scripts, Parts 3, 4 and 5A, 1976 (Box 79)
    - Roots II
      - 12 Reel to Reels, 21 CDs, 9 DAT cassettes: Episodes 1-7, 1979 (Box 101 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_075-095)
      - Betamax Tapes, 1979 (Box 100)
      - Cassette, 1977 (Box 99-100)
      - Cassettes: 52nd Street Tape Duplication - "Roots" II (Reels 1-9), 1977 (Box 99)
      - List of Tracks, Parts 1-7, February, 1979 (Box 84)
      - Reel: Part VII, 196707, Mono Score, 1979 (Box 104)
      - Score, Part I, undated (Box 84)
      - Score, Part II, undated (Box 84)
      - Score, Part III, undated (Box 85)
      - Score, Part IV, undated (Box 85)
      - Score, Part V, 1979 (Box 85)
      - Score, Part VII, 1979 (Box 85)
      - Score and Timing Sheet, Part VI, 1978, undated (Box 85)
      - Script, Part IV, undated (Box 85)
      - VHS Tapes: Parts 1-6, 1979 (Box 102)
    - Roots: The Gift or Roots' Christmas
      - 4 Reel to Reels, 6 CDs, 4 DAT Cassettes: Masters, Isolated Proto, with Slates, 1988 (Box 101 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_096-101)
      - Cassettes: 52nd Street tape duplication - "Roots" Xmas (Reels 1-4), 1977 (Box 99)
      - Score, undated (Box 83)
      - Script and Music Spotting Notes, 1988 (Box 82)
      - VHS Tapes, 1998 (Box 102)
    - Roots: One Year Later
      - 2 Reel to Reels, 6 CDs: Reels 1-2 - Vocals, Proto, Masters, 1978 (Box 102 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_126-129)
      - Score, undated (Box 83)
    - The Seekers
      - Reel to Reel and 4 CDs: Productions #52201-52202, 1979 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_015-018)
      - Score, Episode 1, Production #52201, 1979 (Box 86)
      - Score, Episode 2, Production #52202, 1 of 2, 1979 (Box 86)
      - Score, Episode 2, Production #52202, 2 of 2, 1979 (Box 86)
    - Sex and the Married Woman
      - CDs: Master, Discs 1-2, 1977 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_315-317)
      - Score, 1977 (Box 87>)
    - Shotgun Slade
      - Score, Backtrack Episode, undated (Box 87)
      - Score, "Barbed Wire, keep Out" Episode (Box 88)
      - Score, "The Blue Dog" Episode, undated (Box 88)
      - Score, "Bob Ford" Episode, undated (Box 88)
      - Score, "The Deadfall" Episode, undated (Box 88)
      - Score, "The Deadly Key" Episode, undated (Box 89)
      - Score, "Freight Line" Episode, undated (Box 89)
      - Score, "The Golden Tunnel" Episode, undated (Box 89)
      - Score, "Gunnar Yensen" Episode, undated (Box 89)
      - Score, "Killer's Brand:" Episode, undated (Box 89)
      - Score, "The Lady and the Piano " Episode, undated (Box 90)
      - Score, "Major Trouble" Episode, undated (Box 90)
      - Score, "Marked Money" Episode, undated (Box 90)
      - Score, "The Marrigae Circle" Episode, undated (Box 90)
      - Score, "Mesa of Missing Men", undated (Box 90)
      - Score, Miscellaneous, undated (Box 91)
      - Score, "The Missing Train", undated (Box 91)
      - Score, "Omar the Sign Maker" Episode, undated (Box 91)
      - Score, "A Plate of Death" Episode, undateds (Box 91)
      - Score,"The Pool Shark" Episode, undated (Box 92)
      - Score, Production #13420, undated (Box 93)
      - Score, Production #13427, undated (Box 93)
      - Score, Production #13430, undated (Box 94)
      - Score, Production #13432, undated (Box 94)
      - Score, Production #13437, undated (Box 94)
      - Score, Production #13438, undated (Box 94)
      - Score, "The Ring of Death" Episode, undated (Box 92)
      - Score, "The Safe Crackers", undated (Box 92)
      - Score, "The Spanish Bar", undated (Box 92)
      - Score, "The Stalkers" Episode, undated (Box 93)
      - Score, "The Swindle" Episode, undated (Box 93)
      - Score, "Too Smart to Live" Episode, undated (Box 93)
      - Score from album, 1 of 2, undated (Box 87)
      - Score from album, 2 of 2, undated (Box 87)
    - The Sixth Sense
      - Score, "Once Upon a Chilling" Episode, undated (Box 95)
    - Slaterry's People
      - Score, August 7, 1964 (Box 94)
    - Son-Rise: A Miracle of Love
      - 4 Reel to Reels, 4 CDs: Reels 1-4 - Masters with Slates, 1979 (Box 102 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_147-150)
      - Cassette, 1979 (Box 101)
      - Cassette: "You are Love" - "Son-Rise: A Miracle of Love" Filmway Music, 1979 (Box 99)
      - Score, 1 of 2, undated (Box 94)
      - Score, 2 of 2, undated (Box 95)
    - The Spell
      - Score, undated (Box 95)
    - Square One Television, Math Net Segments
      - Cassette, undated (Box 100)
      - Cassette: Square One TV - Missing Baseball Re-Do, undated (Box 99)
      - Score, 1 of 2, undated (Box 96)
      - Score, 2 of 2, undated (Box 94)
    - Star Trek
      - Cassette: Star Trek - "Amok Time", 1967 (Box 99)
      - Cassette: Star Trek - "Amok Time", "Shore Leave", 1967 (Box 100)
      - Cassette: Star Trek vol. II - Amok Time", 1991 (Box 99)
      - Cassette: Star Trek vol. 3 - from Episodes "Shore Leave" and "The Naked Time", 1966 (Box 99)
      - CD: "Star Trek" Paradise Syndrome, Amok Time, Shore Leave, 1968 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_112)
      - CDs: "Amok Time" Star Trek #1-2, 1967 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_426-427)
      - Score, "Amok Time" Episode, undated (Box 96)
      - Score, "Catspaw" Episode, undated (Box 96)
      - Score, "Eight Themes from Star Trek for Oboe and Piano, 2010 (Box 96)
      - Score, "The Paradise Syndrome" Episode, undated (Box 96)
      - Score, "Ruth" from "Shore Leave" Epsiode, undated (Box 96)
      - Score, "Shore Leave" Episode, undated (Box 96)
    - Testimony of Two Men
      - CDs: 47003 - Part 2, Sequenced Master, Isolated Proto, with Slates, 1977 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_268-270)
      - Score, Unknown Episode, undated (Box 96)
    - T.H.E. Cat
      - Score, Conductor and Supervisor Sheets, 1966 (Box 97)
    - Wagon Train
      - CDs: Episode Production 655A, 1959 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_295)
      - Reel-to-Reel, 1959 (Box 104)
      - Score, Conductor Sheets, undated (Box 97)
    - Whispering Smith
      - Score, Booth Sheets, Unknown Episode, undated (Box 97)
      - Score, "The Interpreter" Episode, undated (Box 97)
    - The Wild and the Free
      - Score, undated (Box 97)